

# Sarfraj Lakdawala

•		
Bharuch, India	9033494918	04/05/1987
<b>@</b>	<b>▶</b>	in
Married	Indian	View my Profile

Passionate Digital Marketer with 9 yrs experience in handling Digital strategy planning, Search Engine Optimization, Content Marketing, Social Media, Paid Marketing and more. Excellent analytical, organizational and decision-making abilities and provide leadership and vision which drives teams to meet goals.

# **Professional Experience**

01/2014 – present Vadodara, India

### Sr. Digital Marketing Strategist, Upnexo Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

- Build and implement effective SEO strategies
- Create campaigns in Google Ads and manage ads
- Create campaigns in Facebook adverts and manage ads
- Manage a team of content writers and developers
- Re-branded site to improve websites growth
- Improved website speed using of GTmetrix
- Managing & Reviewing Google Search Console and Analytics reports Ensure timely delivery of all reporting
- Solved technical errors
- Competitors Analysis
- A/B Testing
- Content Marketing
- Manage Social Media Optimization
- Created AMP pages
- Manage link building campaign

Note: I have stopped work on this project since 2015, and started working on other projects that detail I have added in the 'Projects' section below.

08/2012 – 12/2013 Padra, Vadodara, India

#### SEO Executive, Swiss Pack Pvt. Ltd

I had optimized the Packaging & Bottle labels websites in this company from the scratch.

- Increased Search Engine traffic
- Performed keyword research and improved keywords ranking
- Built, implemented and updated effective SEO strategies
- Manage On-page, Off-page and Technical SEO
- Increased traffic and leads using Pinterest
- Collaborated with my team to investigate critical SEO-related issues and provided impact solutions

03/2012 – 06/2012 Vadodara, India

### Part Time Jr. PHP Developer, Virtual Solution Pvt. Ltd

- Worked on Client site (copy of the site http://www.easygetjob.6te.net/)
- Knowledge of CSS and HTML

05/2011 – 02/2012 Vadodara, India

### Jr. SEO Executive, Black ID Solutions Pvt. Ltd

- Directory submission
- Article submission
- · Social bookmarking
- Whole Off-page optimization

# **Projects**

# 11/2015 - present

# HostingPill.com, Digital Marketing Strategist

- Identified issues, analyzed information and provide solutions to problems.
- Improve Site's Conversion Rate
- Built this site on WordPress
- Manage a team of content writers and developers
- Increased organic traffic by from 0 to number 50,000 per month
- · Manage on-site and off-site SEO
- Manage WordPress related issues
- Research and implement content recommendations for organic SEO success
- Develop and implement link building strategy
- Recommend changes for website architecture, content, internal linking and other factors to improve SEO positions for target keywords
- Developed Hub & Spoke internal linking strategies
- Managed paid digital marketing campaigns across AdWords, Facebook, Quora and Reddit
- · Manage Social media marketing
- Developed title tag, and description to improve CTR
- Reviewing and analyzing competitors sites to incorporate best practice and creating a marketing strategy
- Managing Technical SEO using Ahrefs site audit & Search console issues
- Tracking links click using Google tag manager
- Improvement in Content design
- Content Marketing
- Manage experiments
- Web Stories Knowledge for implementing
- · Performs other duties as assigned

#### 01/2017 - present

#### ReviewRoller.com

- Build and implement effective SEO strategies
- Coordinate with the web designer and developers to create site's better UI to improve websites growth
- Keywords/Topics research
- Managing content writers
- Monthly reporting of website organic traffic, ranking and goals

08/2015 - present

#### Splitscreenapp.com

- Increase Apps Sells
- Planning SEO/SEM, social media, and Content Strategy
- Outreach to Youtubers for App promotion (it worked)
- Outreach to bloggers for app placement in their posts (it worked)
- A/B testing of landing pages using Google optimize
- Managed Facebook ads
- Manage Display and Videos Ads

01/2014 - 03/2014

#### **Island Swimwear Australia**

- Managed client site Local SEO
- Managed Social media marketing

This client was bound with us for only 3 months.

#### **Education**

04/2010

Pune, India

Master in Computer Management, Pune University

04/2008 India

B. Com., Gujarat University

#### **Skills**

- · Team management
- Able to manage and implement Social Media campaigns
- Google Analytics, Google AdWords, Search console
- Google Tag Manager, Google Optimize

- HTML
- Analytical and Problem-Solving skills
- · Conversion optimization
- Facebook ads

- Content Marketing
- Email Marketing
- WordPress/Javascript/CSS
- Schema

# Languages

• Hindi, English, Gujarati

# Strength:

- I can work sincerely, with strong leadership, honestly & with the patient.
- I am disciplined; I am a loyal and trustworthy employee
- Decision making & problem-solving skills
- I can adapt the new environment for my development fast.
- I am confident, creative with my work.

### **Address**

32, Moral Highland 2, Near Muslim Society, Bharuch- 392001, Gujarat, India

# **Declaration**

I hereby declare that all the statements given above are correct and true on behalf of my knowledge. If a chance is given to me, I am sure that I will do my best towards my work and conduct.

Sartrijk

# **Thank You**

Sarfraj Lakdawala Bharuch, Gujarat, India